Excuse me
Is Mr. Zhu Yihai here?
Brother Zhu helped me out the other day
I came especially to thank him
Room 302 has the answer you want
Jingjing
Coming, coming
In such a hurry
Playing hard to get, huh
Jingjing
Jiao Jing
Jiao
Dahai
I'm taking Jiao Jing with me
See you at the usual spot
What's the rush?
Wait, it's you?
What?
Am I not good enough?
Nothing wrong with that
It's just...
I didn't expect it, that's all
Isn't it cold outside?
Wearing so little
These muscles of yours
You really worked them out well
This tattoo
So manly
Of course
I'm a badass, you know
You badasses' tattoos
are all stick-ons, aren't they?
Enough.
Don't worry if mine's a stick-on or not.
I came today to tell you
stay away from Brother Hai.
Xiong Dali.
What?
You trying to scare me?
Yeah, I'm scaring you.
Staying up in the middle of the night,
just to scare a woman like me.
Xiong Dali,
I thought you were a real man.
This is all you've got?
You...
You think I won't beat you up?
Oh-ho.
That tough, huh?
Come on, hit me, hit me.
Xiong Dali,
you can't control Zhu Yihai,
so you come after me?
Aren't you something.
Don't push me.
Push you?
As if you're worth it.
Fine.
As long as you know.
Just wait.
Xiong Dali,
if you've really got the guts,
make sure Zhu Yihai never sees me
for the rest of his life.
Are you a real man or not?
You asked for this.
The usual spot.
Freezing to death.
Weren't you off doing karaoke with Jiao Jing?
What, not so OK anymore?
You think Jiao Jing and I are for real?
I was just acting.
Turns out Jiao Jing didn't play along,
but Dali bought it completely.
What?
What happened?
Something's gone down.
Take a look.
What is this?
Xiong Dali kidnapped someone.
Has he lost his mind?
He better not do anything stupid.
Because if he does,
it could end up being, you know what.
What "you know what"?
The death penalty.
What?
That serious?
Straight to the death penalty.
Damn.
I could hear you shouting from the back kitchen.
Hurry up and find Dali
before he does anything stupid.
Hey, wait,
where's the usual spot?
I sure as hell don't know.
Where is it?
I don't know either.
Is it that place?
I just got off the plane.
I'll handle the Zhu Yihai situation.
What?
You let him get the Aimin Street Agreement?
You're really losing it in your old age.
From now on, factory matters,
don't go making decisions on your own.
I'll handle them.
No need to take some things too seriously.
Brother Xiong,
I can give you what you want.
Let me tell you,
that act doesn't work on me.
Stay away from Brother Hai.
Don't think I don't know what you're up to.
Xiong Dali,
do you know kidnapping is against the law?
Even if it is,
I can't let you hurt Brother Hai.
Is he worth it?
For Brother Hai,
I'd do anything.
Section Chief Dao
Want me to chase Xiong Dali off?
His dad ran off with some woman a while back
leaving him and his mom behind.
And because of it, his mom
ended up dying on the job.
If that happened to you,
would I chase you off?
So what's he after, then?
His dad took all the money when he left.
He doesn't even have money for the burial.
What do you think he's after?
You can lend to him if you want, I won't.
A fish rots from the head,
he's probably no good either.
You bunch...
Get up.
Dali.
Take this.
If you're helping me,
I don't have any money.
Just take it.
Don't make me beat you up.
Give me the money.
What about Huilian?
Who are you looking down on?
Just take it.
Keep it on you.
From now on, you're my bro.
If you're looking for a bro, count me in too.
My dad got someone to find Auntie a good spot.
Don't worry.
Brother Hai
Let this necklace be our proof
From this day on
we're sworn brothers
True brothers, in our hearts
In our hearts
And you?
Who'd be brothers with you?
True brothers, for life
Agreed
Forget it
Looks like I can't pull off this mission
Mission?
So you really do have a mission
Talk
Spit it out
Ge Zhendong sent me
He told me to drive a wedge
between you and Zhu Yihai
Who knew you two were this close?
Ge Zhendong?
No way
You think I'm stupid?
You got any proof?
Believe me or not
everything I'm saying is true
I know all the dirty stuff Ge Zhendong's done
The proof
is at the head of the guesthouse bed
The evidence is all there
Every bit of it
The truth you're looking for
you can go grab it anytime
But I have one request
You've gotta promise me
Don't tell Yihai, okay?
My feelings for him are real
Yihai's been through enough
Don't drag him into this too, okay?
I'm begging you, Brother Xiong
Brother Xiong
They all say Xiong Dali's got no brains
But right now I feel scary smart
Brother Xiong
Brother Hai, watch me handle this one
You're here
Where's Dali?
Talk
I don't know
Didn't Xiong Dali say
he was prepping some surprise for you?
Surprise?
We've got trouble, Huilian
Let's go
Drive safe, okay?
Where are we headed?
Jing'an Guesthouse
Got it